<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="ancef">Ancef</string>
    <string name="aspirin">Aspirin</string>
    <string name="ativan">Ativan</string>
    <string name="avelox">Avelox</string>
    <string name="benadryl">Benadryl</string>
    <string name="cipro">Cipro</string>
    <string name="catapres">Catapres</string>
    <string name="decadron">Decadron</string>
    <string name="digoxin">Digoxin</string>
    <string name="diprivan">Diprivan</string>
    <string name="dilaudid">Dilaudid</string>
    <string name="haldol">Haldol</string>
    <string name="heparin">Heparin</string>
    <string name="lasix">Lasix</string>
    <string name="lopressor">Lopressor</string>
    <string name="lovenox">Lovenox</string>
    <string name="morphine">Morphine</string>
    <string name="motrin">Motrin</string>
    <string name="nitroglycerin">Nitroglycerin</string>
    <string name="percocet">Percocet</string>
    <string name="phenergan">Phenergan</string>
    <string name="plavix">Plavix</string>
    <string name="prednisone">Prednisone</string>
    <string name="reglan">Reglan</string>
    <string name="rocephin">Rocephin</string>
    <string name="solu_medrol">Solu-medrol</string>
    <string name="tylenol">Tylenol</string>
    <string name="toradol">Toradol</string>
    <string name="unasyn">Unasyn</string>
    <string name="valium">Valium</string>
    <string name="vicodin">Vicodin</string>
    <string name="zithromax">Zithromax</string>
    <string name="zofran">Zofran</string>
    <string name="zosyn">Zosyn</string>
    <string name="adenosine">Adenosine</string>
    <string name="amoxicillin">Amoxicillin</string>
    <string name="ambien">Ambien</string>
    <string name="atenolol">Atenolol</string>
    <string name="augmentin">Augmentin</string>
    <string name="bactrim">Bactrim</string>
    <string name="clindamycin">Clindamycin</string>
    <string name="coumadin">Coumadin</string>
    <string name="compazine">Compazine</string>
    <string name="dilantin">Dilantin</string>
    <string name="diltiazem">Diltiazem</string>
    <string name="dopamine">Dopamine</string>
    <string name="epinephrine">Epinephrine</string>
    <string name="fentanyl">Fentanyl</string>
    <string name="flagyl">Flagyl</string>
    <string name="flomax">Flomax</string>
    <string name="keflex">Keflex</string>
    <string name="levaquin">Levaquin</string>
    <string name="linsiopril">Linsiopril</string>
    <string name="narcan">Narcan</string>
    <string name="oxycdone">Oxycdone</string>
    <string name="oxybutynin">Oxybutynin</string>
    <string name="spironolactone">Spironolactone</string>
    <string name="versed">Versed</string>
    <string name="xanax">Xanax</string>
    <string name="albuterol">Albuterol</string>
    <string name="gi_cocktail">GI Cocktail</string>

    <string name="albuterol_description">This medicine helps patient to breathe easier.  Albuterol opens up the small airways in the lungs to allow air to flow in easier. </string>
    <string name="gi_cocktail_description">This is a group of 2 or 3 medications.  The patient drinks them to help with pain and burning they have in their chest or upper part of their abdomen.  Doctors give these medications when they think a patient is having heart burn or acid reflux.  </string>
    <string name="ancef_description">A cephalosporin antibiotic.  Ancef is used to treat infections.  It may also used before or during surgery to prevent infection.  </string>
    <string name="aspirin_description">Used to treat pain, fevers, and reduce inflammation.  It also has other uses such as preventing heart attacks, strokes and chest pains if prescribed by a doctor.</string>
    <string name="ativan_description">A benzodiazepine used to treat anxiety.  Ativan may also be used for nausea, migraines and seizures.  </string>
    <string name="avelox_description">An antibiotic in the group of drugs called fluoroquinolone.  Avelox drug fights infection on the skin, in the sinuses, lungs or stomach.</string>
    <string name="benadryl_description">An antihistamine used to treat allergic reactions (hives &amp; rashes).  Benadryl is also used to help patients sleep or relieve migraines.</string>
    <string name="cipro_description">An antibiotic from the group called fluoroquinolones.  Cipro is used to treat infections in the body.  </string>
    <string name="catapres_description">This is mainly used to treat high blood pressure.  Catapres is also used for symptoms of alcohol, nicotine, or benzodiazepine withdrawal.</string>
    <string name="decadron_description">Used to treat inflammation in the body.  Decadron can be taken for things such as swelling, allergic reactions, asthma, kidney problems, skin conditions, or flare-ups of MS (Multiple Sclerosis).</string>
    <string name="digoxin_description">Used to help treat heart failure as well as treat atrial fibrillation.  Digoxin makes the heart beat much stronger and more regular.  </string>
    <string name="diprivan_description">Used during short or long surgical procedures for sedation.  Diprivan is also used in an ER or ICU while patients are breathing on a ventilator.</string>
    <string name="dilaudid_description">This an opioid pain medication.  Dilaudid is used to treat severe levels of pain.   </string>
    <string name="haldol_description">Primarily used to treat psychiatric disorders.  Haldol is used to treat symptoms of nausea. </string>
    <string name="heparin_description">An anticoagulant (blood thinner) which prevents formation of blood clots.  These blood clots form form in the legs, arms, lungs, heart or brain.  </string>
    <string name="lasix_description">Most commonly referred to as a “water pill”.  Lasix is used by patients with CHF (Congestive Heart Failure), liver disease, kidney disorders and high blood pressure.   </string>
    <string name="lopressor_description">In the class called beta blockers.  Lopressor is used to treat chest pain, high blood pressure and heart failure.  Using this medication to lower blood pressure can help to prevent strokes, kidney problems and heart attacks.  </string>
    <string name="lovenox_description">Prevents formation of blood clots.  Lovenox is used to treat or prevent deep vein thrombosis (DVT) and blood clots in the lungs (pulmonary embolisms).   </string>
    <string name="morphine_description">A narcotic pain medication used for moderate or severe pain.  Moprhine can be taken orally, through an IV or as an injection into the muscle.   </string>
    <string name="motrin_description">An NSAID (nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug) used to treat pain.  Motrin also reduces swelling and fevers.   </string>
    <string name="nitroglycerin_description">A nitrate used to prevent chest pain (angina) which occurs when the heart does not get enough blood.  Nitroglycerin opens the blood vessels wider to make it easier for blood to get through the body.  </string>
    <string name="percocet_description">An opioid pain medication with both acetaminophen (tylenol) an oxycodone.  Percocet is used to treat moderate to severe pain.</string>
    <string name="phenergan_description">A medication used to help treat and prevent nausea and vomiting.  Phenergan can also be used to help with sleep or with allergy symptoms (ex. rash or itching. </string>
    <string name="plavix_description">This medication is a blood thinner.  Plavix is primarily used to prevent stroke, heart attacks, and other heart problems. </string>
    <string name="prednisone_description">A steroid that helps with swelling. Prednisone is used to treat arthritis, breathing problems, or allergic reactions.  </string>
    <string name="reglan_description">A medication that helps the stomach work better.  Raglan is also used for heartburn or nausea.  </string>
    <string name="rocephin_description">A cephalosporin antibiotic.  Rocephin is used to treat a wide range of infections inside of the body.   </string>
    <string name="solu_medrol_description">A steroid which prevents swelling.  Solu Medrol is used to treat arthritis, inflammation in the intestines, stomach, lungs and problems with allergies.     </string>
    <string name="tylenol_description">Used to treat pain and fevers.  </string>
    <string name="toradol_description">An NSAID (non steroidal anti-inflammatory drug) which treats pain and swelling in the body.   </string>
    <string name="unasyn_description">A antibiotic that are used to fight against bacteria in the body.  Unasyn is given though an IV catheter into the blood.  </string>
    <string name="valium_description">A benzodiazepine, used to treat anxiety.  Valium also treat alcohol withdrawal, and muscle spasms.</string>
    <string name="vicodin_description">An opioid pain medication.  Vicodin is made with both tylenol (acetaminophen) and hydrocodone.  Used to treat mild to severe pain.     </string>
    <string name="zithromax_description">An antibiotic used to treat infections.   Zithromax is used to treat lung, skin, and ear infections as well as pelvic inflammatory disease (PID).</string>
    <string name="zofran_description">Used to prevent or treat nausea and vomiting.</string>
    <string name="zosyn_description">Antibiotic used to treat infections in the body.  Zosyn is commonly used for urine, joint, skin and lung infections (pneumonia). </string>
    <string name="adenosine_description"> An anti arrhythmic drug used to treat irregular heartbeats.  Adenosine is also used to slow the rate of the heart and convert it to a normal rhythm.   </string>
    <string name="amoxicillin_description">An antibiotic used to treat bacteria infections.  This medication treats lung, throat, skin, nose, ear and urine infections.   </string>
    <string name="ambien_description"> A medication in the drug class called sedatives.  It’s used to help people with who have difficulty sleeping.    </string>
    <string name="atenolol_description"> A medication in the group of drugs called Beta Blockers.  These medications affect the heart and circulation of the blood.  It is used to treat high blood pressure, chest pain and reduce the chance of heart attacks.  </string>
    <string name="augmentin_description"> An antibiotic used to treat bacteria within the body. Augmentin is frequently used to treat sinus, lung and urine infections. </string>
    <string name="bactrim_description"> An antibiotic used to treat bacteria infections in the body.  Bactrim is often used to treat diarrhea, urine, lung and ear infections. </string>
    <string name="clindamycin_description">  An antibiotic that is used to treat bacterial infections in the body.  It\'s commonly used to treat dental problems or infections in the mouth or throat.  </string>
    <string name="coumadin_description"> An anticoagulant, also known as a blood thinner.  It is used to prevent strokes, blood clots, and prevent heart attacks.  If a patient is taking coumadin, they will have regularly scheduled blood tests to make sure the INR (blood test) is within a predefined range.     </string>
    <string name="compazine_description"> An anti-psychotic and nausea medication.  Compazine is used to treat anxiety.  It can also be used for nausea, vomiting and psychiatric problems.  </string>
    <string name="dilantin_description"> An anticonvulsant medication.  It’s used to slow the activity in the brain to decrease the chances of seizures.   </string>
    <string name="diltiazem_description"> A calcium channel blocker medication.  It is used to treat high blood pressure, chest pain and abnormal heart rhythms such as atrial fibrillation.  </string>
    <string name="dopamine_description"> A drug that helps improve the pumping strength of the heart. This helps the body to get more blood flow and oxygen.  It is used to treat low blood pressure, kidney problems, heart problems, or other conditions.  </string>
    <string name="epinephrine_description"> A medication used to treat low blood pressure, wheezing, and allergic reactions.  It is used in the emergency department by doctors and nurses.  Some patients also carry an epipen incase they have an allergic reaction to insect stings or food. </string>
    <string name="fentanyl_description"> A narcotic medication used to treat medium to severe pain. .    </string>
    <string name="flagyl_description">An antibiotic used to fight infections in the body.    </string>
    <string name="flomax_description"> A medication that makes it easier to urinate.  It does so by helping to relax the muscles in the bladder and the prostate.  It’s often used for kidney stones or enlarged prostates (a gland near the bladder). </string>
    <string name="keflex_description"> In the group of drugs called cephalosporins.  It is an antibiotic used to treat infections in the body.  Patients take Keflex to treat skin, urinary tract, respiratory infections and others types of infections.  </string>
    <string name="levaquin_description"> An antibiotic in the group of drugs called Floroquinolones.  They are used to fight infections in the body.  Often, levaquin is used to treat bronchitis, pneumonia, kidney infections, or severe infections in the blood. </string>
    <string name="linsiopril_description"> A medication in the class of drugs called Ace Inhibitors.  This medication is primarily used to treat high blood pressure.  </string>
    <string name="narcan_description"> A medication used on patients who have taken too much opioid pain medicine.   It reverses the effects of the opioid.   </string>
    <string name="oxycdone_description"> A medicine in the class of drugs called opioids.  Oxycodone is used to treat mild or severe pain.  </string>
    <string name="oxybutynin_description"> Commonly used for bladder muscle spasms.  The medication helps patients to urinate normally.  </string>
    <string name="spironolactone_description"> iCommonly known as a “water pill”.  It’s different from other “water pills” because it saves important cells called potassium from leaving the body when the patient urinates.  It is primarily used by patients with heart problems (congestive heart failure).</string>
    <string name="versed_description"> A drug in the class called benzodiazepines.  Versed is used for sedation during many short medical procedures.  </string>
    <string name="xanax_description"> In the class of drugs called benzodiazepines.  Xanax is used to treat anxiety, depression and panic disorders. </string>

    <string name="ancef_expanded">cefazolin</string>
    <string name="aspirin_expanded">acetylsalicylic acid</string>
    <string name="ativan_expanded">lorazepam</string>
    <string name="avelox_expanded">moxifloxacin</string>
    <string name="benadryl_expanded">diphenhydramine</string>
    <string name="cipro_expanded">ciprofloxacin</string>
    <string name="catapres_expanded">clonidine</string>
    <string name="decadron_expanded">dexamethasone</string>
    <string name="digoxin_expanded">lanoxin</string>
    <string name="diprivan_expanded">propofol</string>
    <string name="dilaudid_expanded">hydromorphone</string>
    <string name="haldol_expanded">haloperidol</string>
    <string name="heparin_expanded">blood thinner</string>
    <string name="lasix_expanded">congestive heart failure</string>
    <string name="lopressor_expanded">metoprolol</string>
    <string name="lovenox_expanded">pulmonary embolisms</string>
    <string name="motrin_expanded">nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug</string>
    <string name="nitroglycerin_expanded">angina</string>
    <string name="percocet_expanded">tylenol</string>
    <string name="phenergan_expanded">promethazine</string>
    <string name="plavix_expanded">clopidogrel</string>
    <string name="reglan_expanded">metoclopramide</string>
    <string name="rocephin_expanded">ceftriaxone</string>
    <string name="solu_medrol_expanded">methylprednisolone</string>
    <string name="tylenol_expanded">acetaminophen</string>
    <string name="toradol_expanded">nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug</string>
    <string name="unasyn_expanded">ampicillin and sulbactam</string>
    <string name="valium_expanded">diazepam</string>
    <string name="vicodin_expanded">tylenol</string>
    <string name="zithromax_expanded">PID</string>
    <string name="zofran_expanded">ondansetron</string>
    <string name="zosyn_expanded">piperacillin &amp; tazobactam</string>
    <string name="adenosine_expanded">Adenocard</string>
    <string name="amoxicillin_expanded">amoxil</string>
    <string name="ambien_expanded">zolpidem</string>
    <string name="atenolol_expanded">Tenormin</string>
    <string name="augmentin_expanded">amoxicillin &amp; clavulanate potassium</string>
    <string name="bactrim_expanded">sulfamethoxazole &amp; trimethoprim</string>
    <string name="clindamycin_expanded">Cleocin HCl</string>
    <string name="coumadin_expanded">warfarin</string>
    <string name="compazine_expanded">prochlorperazine</string>
    <string name="dilantin_expanded">phenytoin</string>
    <string name="diltiazem_expanded">Cardizem</string>
    <string name="dopamine_expanded">Intropin</string>
    <string name="epinephrine_expanded">Adrenalin</string>
    <string name="fentanyl_expanded">Sublimaze</string>
    <string name="flagyl_expanded">metronidazole</string>
    <string name="flomax_expanded">Flomax</string>
    <string name="keflex_expanded">cephalexin</string>
    <string name="levaquin_expanded">Levofloxacin</string>
    <string name="linsiopril_expanded">Prinivil</string>
    <string name="narcan_expanded">Naloxone</string>
    <string name="oxycdone_expanded">Oxycontin</string>
    <string name="oxybutynin_expanded">Ditropan XL</string>
    <string name="spironolactone_expanded">Aldactone</string>
    <string name="versed_expanded">Midazolam</string>
    <string name="xanax_expanded">Alprazolam</string>
</resources>