<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="ancef">Ancef</string>
    <string name="aspirin">Aspirin</string>
    <string name="ativan">Ativan</string>
    <string name="avelox">Avelox</string>
    <string name="benadryl">Benadryl</string>
    <string name="cipro">Cipro</string>
    <string name="catapres">Catapres</string>
    <string name="decadron">Decadron</string>
    <string name="digoxin">Digoxin</string>
    <string name="diprivan">Diprivan</string>
    <string name="dilaudid">Dilaudid</string>
    <string name="haldol">Haldol</string>
    <string name="heparin">Heparin</string>
    <string name="lasix">Lasix</string>
    <string name="lopressor">Lopressor</string>
    <string name="lovenox">Lovenox</string>
    <string name="morphine">Morphine</string>
    <string name="motrin">Motrin</string>
    <string name="nitroglycerin">Nitroglycerin</string>
    <string name="percocet">Percocet</string>
    <string name="phenergan">Phenergan</string>
    <string name="plavix">Plavix</string>
    <string name="prednisone">Prednisone</string>
    <string name="reglan">Reglan</string>
    <string name="rocephin">Rocephin</string>
    <string name="solu_medrol">Solu-medrol</string>
    <string name="tylenol">Tylenol</string>
    <string name="toradol">Toradol</string>
    <string name="unasyn">Unasyn</string>
    <string name="valium">Valium</string>
    <string name="vicodin">Vicodin</string>
    <string name="zithromax">Zithromax</string>
    <string name="zofran">Zofran</string>
    <string name="zosyn">Zosyn</string>


    <string name="ancef_description">A cephalosporin antibiotic.  It is used to treat bacterial infections.  It may also used before or during surgery to prevent infection.  </string>
    <string name="aspirin_description">Used to treat pain, fevers, and reduce inflammation.  It also has secondary uses such as preventing heart attacks, strokes and chest pains if prescribed by a doctor.</string>
    <string name="ativan_description">A benzodiazepine used to treat anxiety disorders.  It may also be used for nausea, migraines and seizures.  </string>
    <string name="avelox_description">An antibiotic in the group of drugs called fluoroquinolone.  This drug fights infection on the skin, in the sinuses, lungs or stomach.</string>
    <string name="benadryl_description">An antihistamine used to treat allergy symptoms, hives, rashes and also can be used to help with sleep or migraines.</string>
    <string name="cipro_description">An antibiotic from the group called fluoroquinolones.  It is a type of medicine that treats different bacterial infections in the body.</string>
    <string name="catapres_description">An alpha agonist.  It is mainly used to treat high blood pressure but may also be used for alcohol, nicotine, or benzodiazepine withdrawal as well as migraines.</string>
    <string name="decadron_description">Used to treat inflammation in the body.  It can be used for things such as swelling, allergic reactions, asthma, kidney problems, skin conditions, or flare-ups of MS.</string>
    <string name="digoxin_description">Used to help treat heart failure as well as treat atrial fibrillation.  It makes the heart beat much stronger and more regular.  </string>
    <string name="diprivan_description">Used during general anesthesia for procedures or anesthesia.  It is also used in an ER or ICU setting while patients are using a breathing tube and ventilator for sedation.</string>
    <string name="dilaudid_description">Opioid pain medication used to treat moderate to severe pain.  </string>
    <string name="haldol_description">An antipsychotic medicine used to treat schizophrenia, control motor and speak tics in Tourette’s syndrome and also used to control nausea.</string>
    <string name="heparin_description">is an anticoagulant (blood thinner) which prevents formation of blood clots in the veins, arteries or lungs.</string>
    <string name="lasix_description">A loop diuretic which treats water retention.  Most commonly referred to as a “water pill”, it is used in those with CHF (congestive heart failure), liver disease, kidney disorders and high blood pressure.  </string>
    <string name="lopressor_description">In the class called beta blockers.  It is used to treat chest pain, high blood pressure and heart failure.  Using this medication to lower blood pressure can help to prevent strokes, kidney problems and heart attacks.  </string>
    <string name="lovenox_description">An anticoagulant medication which helps prevent formation of blood clots.  It is also used to treat and/or prevent deep vein thrombosis (DVT) as well as blood clots in the lungs (pulmonary embolisms).  </string>
    <string name="morphine_description">is an narcotic pain reliever used for moderate or severe pain.  It can be taken orally, through an IV or as an injection into the muscle.  </string>
    <string name="motrin_description">An NSAID (nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug) used to treat pain, reduce inflammation and reduce fevers.  </string>
    <string name="nitroglycerin_description">A nitrate used to prevent chest pain (angina) which occurs when the heart does not get enough blood.  It dilates the blood vessels to make it easier for blood to reach the heart.  </string>
    <string name="percocet_description">An opioid pain medication with both acetaminophen (tylenol) an oxycodone.  It is used to treat moderate to severe pain.</string>
    <string name="phenergan_description">A medication used to help treat and prevent nausea and vomiting.  It can also be used to help with sleep or with allergic symptoms like rash or itching. </string>
    <string name="plavix_description">Helps prevent unwanted blood clots.  It is primarily used to prevent blood clots after a heart attack or stroke.</string>
    <string name="prednisone_description">is a corticosteroid which prevents inflammation. This oral medication is mainly used for skin conditions, arthritis, breathing disorders, or allergic reactions.  </string>
    <string name="reglan_description">A medication that speeds up how fast the stomach empties.  It also may be used for heartburn or nausea and vomiting.  </string>
    <string name="rocephin_description">A cephalosporin antibiotic used to treat a wide variety of infections in the body.  </string>
    <string name="solu_medrol_description">A steroid which prevents inflammation.  Given through an IV, this medication is used to treat arthritis, ulcerative colitis, nervous system disorders, lung conditions and many other allergic disorders.   </string>
    <string name="tylenol_description">Used to treat pain and fevers.  </string>
    <string name="toradol_description">An NSAID (nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug) which reduces the pain and inflammation in the body.  </string>
    <string name="unasyn_description">A combination antibiotic that are used to fight against bacteria in the body.</string>
    <string name="valium_description">A benzodiazepine, used to treat anxiety, alcohol withdrawal, or muscle spasms.</string>
    <string name="vicodin_description">An opioid pain medication with both acetaminophen (tylenol) and hydrocodone.  It is used to treat moderate to severe pain.   </string>
    <string name="zithromax_description">An antibiotic used to treat lung infections such as pneumonia, skin infections, ear infections and pelvic inflammatory disease (PID) in women.</string>
    <string name="zofran_description">Used to prevent or treat nausea and vomiting.</string>
    <string name="zosyn_description">Combination antibiotic used to fight against bacertia in the body.  It is commonly used for urinary tract infections, joint infections, skin infections, pneumonia as well as infections in the stomach.  It is not uncommon to receive Zosyn in conjunction with other antibiotics.</string>

    <string name="ancef_expanded">cefazolin</string>
    <string name="aspirin_expanded">acetylsalicylic acid</string>
    <string name="ativan_expanded">lorazepam</string>
    <string name="avelox_expanded">moxifloxacin</string>
    <string name="benadryl_expanded">diphenhydramine</string>
    <string name="cipro_expanded">ciprofloxacin</string>
    <string name="catapres_expanded">clonidine</string>
    <string name="decadron_expanded">dexamethasone</string>
    <string name="digoxin_expanded">lanoxin</string>
    <string name="diprivan_expanded">propofol</string>
    <string name="dilaudid_expanded">hydromorphone</string>
    <string name="haldol_expanded">haloperidol</string>
    <string name="heparin_expanded">blood thinner</string>
    <string name="lasix_expanded">congestive heart failure</string>
    <string name="lopressor_expanded">metoprolol</string>
    <string name="lovenox_expanded">pulmonary embolisms</string>
    <string name="motrin_expanded">nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug</string>
    <string name="nitroglycerin_expanded">angina</string>
    <string name="percocet_expanded">tylenol</string>
    <string name="phenergan_expanded">promethazine</string>
    <string name="plavix_expanded">clopidogrel</string>
    <string name="reglan_expanded">metoclopramide</string>
    <string name="rocephin_expanded">ceftriaxone</string>
    <string name="solu_medrol_expanded">methylprednisolone</string>
    <string name="tylenol_expanded">acetaminophen</string>
    <string name="toradol_expanded">nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug</string>
    <string name="unasyn_expanded">ampicillin and sulbactam</string>
    <string name="valium_expanded">diazepam</string>
    <string name="vicodin_expanded">tylenol</string>
    <string name="zithromax_expanded">PID</string>
    <string name="zofran_expanded">ondansetron</string>
    <string name="zosyn_expanded">piperacillin &amp; tazobactam</string>
</resources>