<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="ancef">Ancef</string>
    <string name="aspirin">Aspirin</string>
    <string name="ativan">Ativan</string>
    <string name="avelox">Avelox</string>
    <string name="benadryl">Benadryl</string>
    <string name="cipro">Cipro</string>
    <string name="catapres">Catapres</string>
    <string name="decadron">Decadron</string>
    <string name="digoxin">Digoxin</string>
    <string name="diprivan">Diprivan</string>
    <string name="dilaudid">Dilaudid</string>
    <string name="haldol">Haldol</string>
    <string name="heparin">Heparin</string>
    <string name="lasix">Lasix</string>
    <string name="lopressor">Lopressor</string>
    <string name="lovenox">Lovenox</string>
    <string name="morphine">Morphine</string>
    <string name="motrin">Motrin</string>
    <string name="nitroglycerin">Nitroglycerin</string>
    <string name="percocet">Percocet</string>
    <string name="phenergan">Phenergan</string>
    <string name="plavix">Plavix</string>
    <string name="prednisone">Prednisone</string>
    <string name="reglan">Reglan</string>
    <string name="rocephin">Rocephin</string>
    <string name="solu_medrol">Solu-medrol</string>
    <string name="tylenol">Tylenol</string>
    <string name="toradol">Toradol</string>
    <string name="unasyn">Unasyn</string>
    <string name="valium">Valium</string>
    <string name="vicodin">Vicodin</string>
    <string name="zithromax">Zithromax</string>
    <string name="zofran">Zofran</string>
    <string name="zosyn">Zosyn</string>

    <string name="adenosine">Adenosine</string>
    <string name="amoxicillin">Amoxicillin</string>
    <string name="ambien">Ambien</string>
    <string name="atenolol">Atenolol</string>
    <string name="augmentin">Augmentin</string>
    <string name="bactrim">Bactrim</string>
    <string name="clindamycin">Clindamycin</string>
    <string name="coumadin">Coumadin</string>
    <string name="compazine">Compazine</string>
    <string name="dilantin">Dilantin</string>
    <string name="diltiazem">Diltiazem</string>
    <string name="dopamine">Dopamine</string>
    <string name="epinephrine">Epinephrine</string>
    <string name="fentanyl">Fentanyl</string>
    <string name="flagyl">Flagyl</string>
    <string name="flomax">Flomax</string>
    <string name="keflex">Keflex</string>
    <string name="levaquin">Levaquin</string>
    <string name="linsiopril">Linsiopril</string>
    <string name="narcan">Narcan</string>
    <string name="oxycdone">Oxycdone</string>
    <string name="oxybutynin">Oxybutynin</string>
    <string name="spironolactone">Spironolactone</string>
    <string name="versed">Versed</string>
    <string name="xanax">Xanax</string>
    <string name="albuterol">Albuterol</string>
    <string name="gi_cocktail">GI Cocktail</string>

    <string name="albuterol_description">A bronchodilator that helps increase flow of air into the airways while it relaxes the muscles in the lungs.</string>
    <string name="gi_cocktail_description">A group of medications usually to help treat symptoms of discomfort occurring in the gastric system.  This is usually given to patients who are experiencing heartburn or acid reflux.</string>
    <string name="ancef_description">A cephalosporin antibiotic.  It is used to treat bacterial infections.  It may also used before or during surgery to prevent infection.  </string>
    <string name="aspirin_description">Used to treat pain, fevers, and reduce inflammation.  It also has secondary uses such as preventing heart attacks, strokes and chest pains if prescribed by a doctor.</string>
    <string name="ativan_description">A benzodiazepine used to treat anxiety disorders.  It may also be used for nausea, migraines and seizures.  </string>
    <string name="avelox_description">An antibiotic in the group of drugs called fluoroquinolone.  This drug fights infection on the skin, in the sinuses, lungs or stomach.</string>
    <string name="benadryl_description">An antihistamine used to treat allergy symptoms, hives, rashes and also can be used to help with sleep or migraines.</string>
    <string name="cipro_description">An antibiotic from the group called fluoroquinolones.  It is a type of medicine that treats different bacterial infections in the body.</string>
    <string name="catapres_description">An alpha agonist.  It is mainly used to treat high blood pressure but may also be used for alcohol, nicotine, or benzodiazepine withdrawal as well as migraines.</string>
    <string name="decadron_description">Used to treat inflammation in the body.  It can be used for things such as swelling, allergic reactions, asthma, kidney problems, skin conditions, or flare-ups of MS.</string>
    <string name="digoxin_description">Used to help treat heart failure as well as treat atrial fibrillation.  It makes the heart beat much stronger and more regular.  </string>
    <string name="diprivan_description">Used during general anesthesia for procedures or anesthesia.  It is also used in an ER or ICU setting while patients are using a breathing tube and ventilator for sedation.</string>
    <string name="dilaudid_description">Opioid pain medication used to treat moderate to severe pain.  </string>
    <string name="haldol_description">An antipsychotic medicine used to treat schizophrenia, control motor and speak tics in Tourette’s syndrome and also used to control nausea.</string>
    <string name="heparin_description">is an anticoagulant (blood thinner) which prevents formation of blood clots in the veins, arteries or lungs.</string>
    <string name="lasix_description">A loop diuretic which treats water retention.  Most commonly referred to as a “water pill”, it is used in those with CHF (congestive heart failure), liver disease, kidney disorders and high blood pressure.  </string>
    <string name="lopressor_description">In the class called beta blockers.  It is used to treat chest pain, high blood pressure and heart failure.  Using this medication to lower blood pressure can help to prevent strokes, kidney problems and heart attacks.  </string>
    <string name="lovenox_description">An anticoagulant medication which helps prevent formation of blood clots.  It is also used to treat and/or prevent deep vein thrombosis (DVT) as well as blood clots in the lungs (pulmonary embolisms).  </string>
    <string name="morphine_description">is an narcotic pain reliever used for moderate or severe pain.  It can be taken orally, through an IV or as an injection into the muscle.  </string>
    <string name="motrin_description">An NSAID (nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug) used to treat pain, reduce inflammation and reduce fevers.  </string>
    <string name="nitroglycerin_description">A nitrate used to prevent chest pain (angina) which occurs when the heart does not get enough blood.  It dilates the blood vessels to make it easier for blood to reach the heart.  </string>
    <string name="percocet_description">An opioid pain medication with both acetaminophen (tylenol) an oxycodone.  It is used to treat moderate to severe pain.</string>
    <string name="phenergan_description">A medication used to help treat and prevent nausea and vomiting.  It can also be used to help with sleep or with allergic symptoms like rash or itching. </string>
    <string name="plavix_description">Helps prevent unwanted blood clots.  It is primarily used to prevent blood clots after a heart attack or stroke.</string>
    <string name="prednisone_description">is a corticosteroid which prevents inflammation. This oral medication is mainly used for skin conditions, arthritis, breathing disorders, or allergic reactions.  </string>
    <string name="reglan_description">A medication that speeds up how fast the stomach empties.  It also may be used for heartburn or nausea and vomiting.  </string>
    <string name="rocephin_description">A cephalosporin antibiotic used to treat a wide variety of infections in the body.  </string>
    <string name="solu_medrol_description">A steroid which prevents inflammation.  Given through an IV, this medication is used to treat arthritis, ulcerative colitis, nervous system disorders, lung conditions and many other allergic disorders.   </string>
    <string name="tylenol_description">Used to treat pain and fevers.  </string>
    <string name="toradol_description">An NSAID (nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug) which reduces the pain and inflammation in the body.  </string>
    <string name="unasyn_description">A combination antibiotic that are used to fight against bacteria in the body.</string>
    <string name="valium_description">A benzodiazepine, used to treat anxiety, alcohol withdrawal, or muscle spasms.</string>
    <string name="vicodin_description">An opioid pain medication with both acetaminophen (tylenol) and hydrocodone.  It is used to treat moderate to severe pain.   </string>
    <string name="zithromax_description">An antibiotic used to treat lung infections such as pneumonia, skin infections, ear infections and pelvic inflammatory disease (PID) in women.</string>
    <string name="zofran_description">Used to prevent or treat nausea and vomiting.</string>
    <string name="zosyn_description">Combination antibiotic used to fight against bacertia in the body.  It is commonly used for urinary tract infections, joint infections, skin infections, pneumonia as well as infections in the stomach.  It is not uncommon to receive Zosyn in conjunction with other antibiotics.</string>


    <string name="adenosine_description"> is an anti arrhythmic drug used to treat irregular heartbeats, slowing the rate of the heart and converting it to a normal rhythm.   </string>
    <string name="amoxicillin_description"> is a penicillin antibiotic used to treat bacertia in the body.  It is primarily used for tonsilitis, bronchitis, pneumonia, gonorrhea and infections of the ear, nose, skin and urinary infections. </string>
    <string name="ambien_description"> is a medication in the drug class of sedatives.  It’s used to help people with insomnia.  </string>
    <string name="atenolol_description"> is a medication in the group of drugs called Beta Blockers.  These medications affect the heart and circulation of the blood.  It is used to treat high blood pressure, chest pain and reduce the chances of a heart attack.  </string>
    <string name="augmentin_description"> is an antibiotic used to treat bacteria within the body.  It’s in the penicillin group of drugs.  It’s commonly used for sinusitis, pneumonia, urinary infections and bronchitis. </string>
    <string name="bactrim_description"> is an antibiotic used to treat different types of bacertia in the body.  It’s commonly used for urinary infections, bronchitis, diarrhea, or ear infections. </string>
    <string name="clindamycin_description">  is an antibiotic that is used to treat bacterial infections in the body </string>
    <string name="coumadin_description"> is an anticoagulant, also known as a blood thinner.  It is used to prevent strokes, blood clots, and prevent heart attacks.  If you’re taking coumadin, you will often need to have your blood checked to make sure your INR (blood test) is within a therapeutic range.  </string>
    <string name="compazine_description"> is a medication used for a wide range of symptoms.  It can be used to treat anxiety, nausea and vomiting as well as psychotic disorders and migraine headaches.  </string>
    <string name="dilantin_description"> is an anticonvulsant drug.  It’s used to slow impulses in the brain that can cause seizures.  </string>
    <string name="diltiazem_description"> is a calcium channel blocker medication.  It is used to treat high blood pressure, chest pain and abnormal heart rhythms such as atrial fibrillation.  </string>
    <string name="dopamine_description"> is drug which helps improve the pumping strength of the heart which creates better blood flow throughout the body.  It is used to treat low blood pressure during a heart attack, kidney failure, heart failure, or other conditions. </string>
    <string name="epinephrine_description"> is a medication used to treat low blood pressure, wheezing, and serious allergic reactions.  It may be used in the emergency setting by medical professionals or by those with serious allergies to insect bites, stings, or foods (epi pen)</string>
    <string name="fentanyl_description"> is an narcotic medication primarily used to treat pain.    </string>
    <string name="flagyl_description"> is an antibiotic used to fight against bacteria in the body.  </string>
    <string name="flomax_description"> is an alpha-blocker medication that helps make it easier to urinate.  It does so by helping to relax the muscles in the bladder and the prostate.  It’s frequently used in cases of kidney stones or enlarged prostates. </string>
    <string name="keflex_description"> is in the group of drugs called cephalosporins.  It is an antibiotic used to treat bacterial infections in the body.  A physician may prescribe Reflex to treat skin infections, urinary tract infections, as well as respiratory infections and others.  </string>
    <string name="levaquin_description"> is an antibiotic in the group of drugs called Floroquinolones.  They are used to fight against bacterial infections in the body.  Frequently this drug is used to treat bronchitis, pneumonia, kidney infections, or during early treatment of sepsis.  </string>
    <string name="linsiopril_description"> is a medication in the class of drugs called Ace Inhibitors.  This medication is primarily used to treat high blood pressure.  </string>
    <string name="narcan_description"> is a medication used to reverse the effects of opioid medication.  It is most frequently used when a person been given or used too much of an opioid medication and is exhibiting the effects of opioid overdose such as altered mental status, decreased breathing pattern, or drowsiness.  </string>
    <string name="oxycdone_description"> is opioid class medication used to treat pain.  </string>
    <string name="oxybutynin_description"> is most commonly used for bladder and urinary tract spasms.  It will help treat overactive bladder, incontinence and frequent urination.  </string>
    <string name="spironolactone_description"> is commonly known as a “water pill”.  It’s different from other “water pills” in that is does not rid the body of potassium.  It is commonly used to treat congestive heart failure or excessive edema (water retention most commonly seen in the lower legs).</string>
    <string name="versed_description"> is a benzodiazepine used for mild sedation during medical procedures.  </string>
    <string name="xanax_description"> is a benzodiazepine used to treat anxiety, depression and panic disorders.</string>


    <string name="ancef_expanded">cefazolin</string>
    <string name="aspirin_expanded">acetylsalicylic acid</string>
    <string name="ativan_expanded">lorazepam</string>
    <string name="avelox_expanded">moxifloxacin</string>
    <string name="benadryl_expanded">diphenhydramine</string>
    <string name="cipro_expanded">ciprofloxacin</string>
    <string name="catapres_expanded">clonidine</string>
    <string name="decadron_expanded">dexamethasone</string>
    <string name="digoxin_expanded">lanoxin</string>
    <string name="diprivan_expanded">propofol</string>
    <string name="dilaudid_expanded">hydromorphone</string>
    <string name="haldol_expanded">haloperidol</string>
    <string name="heparin_expanded">blood thinner</string>
    <string name="lasix_expanded">congestive heart failure</string>
    <string name="lopressor_expanded">metoprolol</string>
    <string name="lovenox_expanded">pulmonary embolisms</string>
    <string name="motrin_expanded">nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug</string>
    <string name="nitroglycerin_expanded">angina</string>
    <string name="percocet_expanded">tylenol</string>
    <string name="phenergan_expanded">promethazine</string>
    <string name="plavix_expanded">clopidogrel</string>
    <string name="reglan_expanded">metoclopramide</string>
    <string name="rocephin_expanded">ceftriaxone</string>
    <string name="solu_medrol_expanded">methylprednisolone</string>
    <string name="tylenol_expanded">acetaminophen</string>
    <string name="toradol_expanded">nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug</string>
    <string name="unasyn_expanded">ampicillin and sulbactam</string>
    <string name="valium_expanded">diazepam</string>
    <string name="vicodin_expanded">tylenol</string>
    <string name="zithromax_expanded">PID</string>
    <string name="zofran_expanded">ondansetron</string>
    <string name="zosyn_expanded">piperacillin &amp; tazobactam</string>


    <string name="adenosine_expanded">Adenocard</string>
    <string name="amoxicillin_expanded">amoxil</string>
    <string name="ambien_expanded">zolpidem</string>
    <string name="atenolol_expanded">Tenormin</string>
    <string name="augmentin_expanded">amoxicillin &amp; clavulanate potassium</string>
    <string name="bactrim_expanded">sulfamethoxazole &amp; trimethoprim</string>
    <string name="clindamycin_expanded">Cleocin HCl</string>
    <string name="coumadin_expanded">warfarin</string>
    <string name="compazine_expanded">prochlorperazine</string>
    <string name="dilantin_expanded">phenytoin</string>
    <string name="diltiazem_expanded">Cardizem</string>
    <string name="dopamine_expanded">Intropin</string>
    <string name="epinephrine_expanded">Adrenalin</string>
    <string name="fentanyl_expanded">Sublimaze</string>
    <string name="flagyl_expanded">metronidazole</string>
    <string name="flomax_expanded">Flomax</string>
    <string name="keflex_expanded">cephalexin</string>
    <string name="levaquin_expanded">Levofloxacin</string>
    <string name="linsiopril_expanded">Prinivil</string>
    <string name="narcan_expanded">Naloxone</string>
    <string name="oxycdone_expanded">Oxycontin</string>
    <string name="oxybutynin_expanded">Ditropan XL</string>
    <string name="spironolactone_expanded">Aldactone</string>
    <string name="versed_expanded">Midazolam</string>
    <string name="xanax_expanded">Alprazolam</string>

</resources>